Fatema Boxwala

My process is lateral and iterative. I research, collect, think and design best when I pursue multiple pathways.

I make with my hands first. I use a mixed media approach to design print and digital artifacts.

My right and left brain collaborate. I approach design from my background in ethnograpy and scientific research.

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts	GRAPHIC DESIGN	College for Creative Studies (CCS)	DETROIT	05/14
Master of Public Health	HEALTH BEHAVIOR & EDUCATION	University of Michigan (UM)	ANN ARBOR	04/08
Bachelor of Arts	CULTURAL ANTHROPOLOGY	University of Michigan	ANN ARBOR	08/06

Experience

Teaching Assistant	CCS GRAPHIC DESIGN DEPT	Critiqued and helped students in type and visual communications courses	09/13-05/14
Graphic Designer	CCS LIBERAL ARTS DEPT	Designed posters for student competitions and new courses	09/10-05/14
Graphic Designer	COMPUWARE + CCS SPONSORED PROJECT	Prototyped and designed a client database and presentation management tool in a team of 7	01/12-05/12
Health Educator	WASHTENAW COUNTY PUBLIC HEALTH DEPARTMENT	Created emergency plans, communicated with healthcare providers and managed vaccine allocations	05/09-07/11
Principal Investigator	UM CANCER EPIDEMIOLOGY EDUC IN SPECIAL POPULATIONS	Researched cancer screening practices, analyzed quantitative data and published findings in a scholarly journal	09/06-12/08

Accolades

CCS Student Exhibition	2010-2014	New Faculty Search Student Representative	2013
CCS Dean's List	2011-2013	UM Dean's Award	2007-2008
CCS Merit Scholarship	2011-2014	UM University Honors	2005-2006